ICC LBA happened, well, today I had a conversation with the CFO of ICC LBA,
Gopal Balachandran sir, on the channel.
Quickly listen to what he has to say,
Pankaj ji, if the trade equations are looking good between HDB and ICC LB, then please let me know,
otherwise I will wait to take your picks, please
tell the CFO sir, I think it is a
great question, so first of all,
thank you so much for having me on the channel
and good morning to all your viewers.  So,
I
want to answer this in context because
if you look at the growth of the industry
in the last so many years, like
when the insurance sector opened in
2001-2002, if you look at the growth till today, the
compounded growth in revenue has been
about 15-16% and the thought process of ICI LBA
in terms of writing growth or
driving the book has been to grow the book
profitably.  So our thinking has been that
wherever we see profitable opportunities,
we obviously kind of go all
out and make sure that we are able to tap
into the opportunity and this is the
thought process which you have seen in FI
26 and your point is absolutely correct.  If you
look at the numbers for the entire year, at an aggregate
level, the industry growth has been roughly around
9.2%. The growth of ICMARD was roughly
around 7%. So, we
can think that the outcome of this is that ICC LB has grown slower than the
market.
I think the CFO is actually answering
the question, I think what actually
happened with ICC LBA. The numbers for Q4 are good, there is
no complaint in premium mobilization, but now when the entire
financial numbers have to be mapped with Q4.
Growth lags behind the industry in full financial year numbers.
Why Four has
better growth than the industry?  So the
CFO was answering why the
growth lagged behind the industry throughout the year?